sloganshub.org 2017-09-29

# Privacy Policy | Slogans Hub

**Privacy Policy for www.sloganshub.com**

**Introduction**

At www.sloganshub.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by

www.sloganshub.com and how it is used.

**What information we collect?**

We save the details you provide to us in your account profile, including your email address, username, password and any other additional information provided by the user. We collect

information about our users or site visitors through Google Analytics such as browser type, operating system, session duration, date & time of visit, IP address and referring website.

**What We Do With this information?**

We will use your email address to update you about SlogansHub news. We will never share your email with any third parties. We use information generated form Google Analytics to

improve website & system administration.

**Who we may disclose collected information to?**

In general, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. We

will disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or

enforce our rights or the rights of another user.

Moreover, we will never sell your information or spam you in any way.

**Privacy Policy Agreement**

By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, you may feel free to e-mail us

with questions or concerns, but your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time.

**Contact Us**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us.
